This kind of thing is really good
and great to finish it
This kind of dream This kind of dream
I wonder
can all dreams
be realized on earth?
Realize it
with the unimaginable omnipotent bag
I want to fly freely in the sky
That's carangid dragonfly
Ah... I like Doraemon the most
Epidemical Viruses
Why is your skirt so long?
How dare you say that?
Damn
you only know the common
female finery impersonation
That's all...
It's useless that you're irritated
because of this
The present female popular finery,
skirt is longer and longer
You really can't keep up with
the popularity
It's really voguish to dress like this
You're on the popular acme
I'm very sensitive to popularity
This way, please
Thanks
Sorry, we're really very thick-skulled
No, I won't go
It's rare to celebrate the homecoming,
you'd better go to join in it
Even if I want to go, but I can't
Because my skirts are all Mini-skirt
You may make a new skirt now
But I have no enough time
I told you last time,
I wanted to make a new dress...
Don't run wild, Nobita,
go to do your homework quickly
I did that already
Then do your homework of tomorrow
No kidding
Isn't what I said right?
Your mustaches are so long,
very cool, right?
But I don't act cool
You'd not better go to call her down
You may do that after the windstorm
But it's very troublesome like this
Who will settle popularity on earth?
I don't know either
In a word, every one
will keep up with popularity
If it's different,
you will feel very uneasy
Let's do an interesting experiment
Epidemical Viruses
We'll breed up this kind of bug
Then tell them
Skirt revert to the popular short skirt
Mini-skirt is popular now
To dress Mini-skirt
is really popular acme
And then make germs to strow with wind
Did you put it on?
Who didn't see...
Hah
How could I dress like this?
It's very shameful,
I dare not to walk in the street
I succeed
I don't want to put on this dress
Wasn't it made just now?
Wasn't it the dress
of the year before last year?
How redoubtable the viruses are!
It's shorter than before
What will you do like this?
Is it shorter than before?
It's Shizuka
Shorter
It'd be shorter than before
You're really salacious
Let's go out to have a look
OK
Nobody
Hah
Well, it must be very short, it's cold
outside, so nobody dare to dress it
It's too poor
Then it'd be more warmer popularity
What about the bell-bottomed pants?
OK, make the trouser widen...
You're very sensitive to popularity
Right
Me too
Let's make more newfangled popularity
OK...
The tattered dress
is very voguish impersonation
It's called moocher dress,
and the toilette like this
It's called Cat Eyes toilette modus
When you go out,
have on a shoe and a slipper
and take a trash can in your hands
when you greet others,
you may say Sesese
and pull a face when you draw apart
Sesese means summer will come soon
You have on the moocher dress too
Yeah, it's very popular now
See you
Don't joke too much
In either case we all dress the same,
nobody feels strange
and the efficacy of the viruses
only have one day
Hey, hurry, or you'll be late
No...
If I don't dress like this,
I'll feel very shameful
What're you saying?
No, I must dress like this, otherwise,
I dare not to walk in the street
It's up to you
He sat with the viruses later,
he couldn't keep up with popularity
It'd not be this result
Visional call system
You've not decided it, it's not OK
You'd better take heart of grace
to make a phone
No, I'm still afraid
But I have to make a phone
What shall I do?
What shall I do on earth?
What're you calling?
I want to let Gian return me my cartoon
Then let him return you, is it OK?
It's not easy just like what you said
It's very hard to let him return you
If Gian's not happy,
and you let him return your book
That'll be terrible
He must say that don't you believe me
OK, if you can't believe me
and make me get rattled,
I won't return you certainly
That's so
Then we'll use this
Visional call system
What's that?
This is a kind of testing system
Connect with telephone
and get on the phone
In fact it's not true
But the screenage of the opponent will
appear, just like we're really calling
so we can know what the opponent
is thinking clearly
This is good
Then I'll call again
Look, it appears
Talk with him
He's not the true Gian
Don't be afraid
Gian, it's not important thing
I wonder when you can return
me that cartoon
That cartoon? Of course I'll return you
Really...
In fact, if I don't return you it,
I'll feel very sorry
And I'm on your home way,
I'll take it to return you
See you
It's really unbelievable
He's not true
but his real thought will appear
in the picture
Hello, thanks for you can take it
to return specially
It's really rare
I never thought you could take it
to return by yourself
In fact, I almost give up half of hope
I won't return you it
You're like this each time
It's really terrible
You said that, of course he got rattled
But I can't give up because of this
you must force Gian return your book
with all kinds of ways
This machine
will be used to train up you
Gian, it's my fault just now
Sorry to trouble you to return me
my book, I beg you
Huh, no
Return me my book
You borrowed it,
but you didn't want to return
you're really terrible
What did you say?
Hang up the telephone, hurry...
It's not OK
Then you'll use of the fawning policy
I believe you
There's right in your heart
you can return what you borrowed
from others certainly
Are you satirizing me?
I don't believe you
I won't return you that book
Doraemon, I couldn't say anything
Don't give up easily,
you may say something at random
Bastard! Return m me my book
If you don't want to return me that book
I'll paste you
and roll you to make pellet
I'm really scared,
nobody dare say that to me
Great, I'll return you that book
ls it really OK?
It doesn't matter, it's right absolutely
Gian, you butterball!
If you don't want to return me that book
I'll paste you
and roll you to make pellet
Ouch!
Because it's different with
what you said just now
Don't look down on it,
because that machine is very sensitive
If he doesn't return me my book
I'll think that
cartoon is very important
I understand you
But it becomes so now,
it'll be harder to decide
My lovely cartoon,
I'll really dispart with you forever
I can understand you
but it's useless
to be careful for the past
Let's play,
I'll go down to you on purpose
I don't want to play
I hide one Rice Cracker,
I'll share half to you
I don't want to eat
Well, you're Kean's fan, right?
Yeah, how's it?
If you can talk with Kean,
you'll be happy, won't you?
What're you saying?
She's a very popular swan,
how could she talk with me...
Right
I'm your fan
I'm very happy, thank you
You're welcome
Don't be so formalistic,
you may say more what you want to say
Would you like to make friend
with me in the future?
Sure, we'll be good friends forever
Great, nice to meet you!
Great!
I've chatted with Kean for an hour
It's really wonderful
Well
Only I monopolize so happy thing,
what a pity!
Everyone,
if you want to chat with the swan
please come to my home
Hello, how are you doing?
Do you want to make friend with me?
OK
Very cool! Mr. Yekowulan
Stand in line...
Ten yen three minutes
And you may chat with
the famous player. Welcome to call
He thought of these things at once
Well, because there're many people now
I beg you
I want to talk about Lily
I'll return you that book, OK?
That's a matter of course
And I'll send you this peg-top book
I beg you
Great
Plant pen
How beautiful! Thank you
I plant the flower with my heart
I don't know you like flowers
very much at all
If you like flowers, it shows
your heart is very simpleminded
Pose
Mom
I want to like and plant flowers
I planted petunia last year,
but you didn't help me at all
it scorched later,
I don't know that's whose mistake
What flower do you want to plant?
As long as it's flower, that's OK
If that's so
you'd like to bring it out
Look
It's pictured
You show this kind of attitude,
is it OK?
Don't you want to send
Shizuka some flowers?
Yeah
You'd better conduct an experiment
you must picture the flower first
After you picture it, color
and knead the sheet like this
This is seed
Seed?
Right, make this inter in the flowerpot
And water it, that'll be over
Then how's it?
Wait to see
This is plant pen
No matter it's flower or tree
it'll grow up just like what you picture
As long as you water it more,
it'll grow up more
But that flower
was pictured omnivorously
It's pictured omnivorously
you must look at the graph
to picture carefully
OK, it's finished
Knead it troupe to inter the mould
How beautiful!
How to plant
and make it very beautiful like this?
How to say?
After all, it's because
I like flowers very much
It's easy to get that kind of flower
If it's Shizuka, she'll make
more beautiful flowers
I hope that very much
What? Plant pen?
It seems that it's very funny,
please let me have a try
OK, you may picture it at once
Here you are
It's finished
I pictured many flowers in a minute
I won Suneo
Huh
ls anyone talking about me?
I'm knowledgeable and well-bred
Of course someone will talk about me
But there'd not be
this kind of flower in Nobita's home
He might buy it in flowers shop,
I'll go to laugh at him
Good grief!
You're really Shizuka, how beautiful!
I hope I can be surrounded
by flowers like this one time
OK, I'll go to picture it Let's go
Go to picture it
Ouch...
Bastard!
Ouch! Suneo
Sorry! Don't run
Don't run
Don't run, Suneo
You planted a very big tree
I wonder what kind of flowers it'll have
Please wait and see
ls it nice?
OK, I'll plant an interesting tree too
But the most important is the paper
I found it
( Great washer on sale)
Why do you irrigate so much water
Don't ask about that
Pour that barrel of water down
Then please wait
What a big tree
ls this our house?
Please come in and have a look
OK
Wow...
This is my room
This is a bed
How can we put on a wooden clothes
Wooden teapot and wooden cup
Let's sit down here
and have a cup of tea
But it's very dull only to drink tea
There's some snack in the cabinet,
I'll go to get some
OK
Earthquake, earthquake...
Now you can drain
Sorry I drew on the back
of the ad paper of the washer
To perform in TV with the touch camera
This is Nobi's home
Go to watch TV at once
What
Don't you know now?
Go to change the channel
Yes...
What're you doing?
Someone asked me to change the channel
Who?
Yeah, who is he?
It's just that...
I often heard his voice
Do you bring him to mind?
I'm Suneo in grade 4 this year
It's just this one
It's Suneo
Great, he appeared in TV
It's the singing contest of children
I have a lot of happiness
He sings very well
Great
It's too senseless
The kid is that one in TV
It's cool
I hope he can pass the test
Do you feel upset?
Suneo is very popular
A moment please
I want to get his signature
Nobita
What do you feel
when you see his attitude?
Right, I envy him
You're too useless
I mean
you don't want to take part in it?
It's impossible for me
No, you can
Only with my skill?
Really?
Yeah
I'll make you popular
To let you not lose to any one
in Japanese children
is my mission
It's really hopeful
I'm very glad
Great, so many people want his signature
Don't worry, you'll become that too
Hey, everybody
Nobita will perform in TV too now
It won't be so easy
I agree with you
I feel that too
No problem, I'll make you appear in TV
You may not pay performance outlay, as
long as you can let Nobita appear on TV
Let him appear on TV at once
That's important
Why?
They have so many TV channels,
let you appear on one, isn't it OK?
Here's...
You're so weak, it's not good
No
What's the matter?
Here's...
Then I'll appear on TV, OK?
I really can't depend on him,
is it really no problem?
Do you want to get on the singing match
of children edition?
But because
there's too many people to sign up
Please line up to join in
the preliminary heat
There're so many people
You're toilsome, next one
Yeah...
Please say out your name and age
My name is... Nobi Nobita
Please sing
Nobi
I'm really left in the basket
However, I still can't appear on TV
It's Nobita, I watched TV
but you didn't appear at all
I thought it'd be very strange
if Nobita appeared on TV
You're good at lying
He'll appear on TV,
and he'll make program soon
Which channel?
All channels
Then from what time?
Then the next is Nobita show
just screen only Nobita
Doraemon,
do you stretch your blanket?
No, I don't
Touch type vidicon
Great, it's like true
Right?
You may touch the vidicon
Like this?
OK, wait for me a moment
The universe TV station will be opened
Nobita show is waiting
for your appreciation
Does he really appear on TV?
I'll go to watch at once
I'm watching it
But what's he doing on earth?
He's been napping
I have no way to deal with him
Nobita, the vidicon has screened you,
you'd perform something
It's screened you since just now
How shameful!
I don't want to be screened
How shameful! Don't screen me...
I said I didn't want to be screened...
He has only eluded...
It's a mistake to let him appear on TV
OK, I'll appear on TV
Help! Come to touch the vidicon quickly
I touched it
Screen me, follow me please
I have a lot of happiness
To watch TV is more relaxed
Damn! I'll go to get back the vidicon
You meant that Suneo got back
the vidicon, didn't you?
Please wait a moment
Suneo, return the vidicon to others
It's screening me
ls it playing on TV?
I wanted to appear on TV
It's too slow
(What's the matter... )
Return me the vidicon
We'll use it to screen Nobita...
and we're using it now...
It's headache
Doraemon, I closed the switch,
but it's still playing
It's useless to watch
this kind of program, let's go out
The program of today is very strange
It's screened Suneo's face
Someone must trick him
Suneo, we're all playing outside,
nobody’s watching TV
What?
It's really vapid!
You'd better stop performing
And I won't either
What vidicon?
Wait... Mom
Why do you course me?
Don't screen me...
I said that
Help!
Hey, you'd take up your pitches
ls anyone here?
Come to help me quickly
Nobita, Suneo's calling help
What happened?
In a word, let him return us the vidicon
OK
Don't come in
I'll piss, I'll piss at once
I refrain myself now
Please wait outside
We're screening him
Then we have to wait a moment OK
It floats in the sky
Mom, if you don't want to have
this plastic bag, please give me
OK
What will you use it to make?
You'll know after you look at it
Fold it like this...
Trim off the above part
of the conduplicate bag like this
Open and smooth it like this.
Then stick the same long rope with the
sellotape at the verge of the bag.
Tie something heavy at the bottom of it.
Look, the parachute is finished!
WOW!
You did it...very successful!
Good...
Doraemon, if we can sit on it,
that'll be very great!
We can!
By this!
Deflating Lamp!
Right!
To deflate our shapes by it,
that'll be ok!
That's too great!
In this case, we'll be able to get
on the parachute!
I'll take you to the high, you'd better
tie the parachute tightly!
Yep!
Good, I'm ready!
Doraemon, rely on you!
Okay!
So high!
It's all right, you can jump down!
I'm jumping!
I did it...So cool!
Really interesting.
Next I want to jump from higher place.
How about from the eave?
Much higher...
I want to jump from much higher place!
The place much higher than the eave...
So just jump down from the plane like
the true bailing, how about it?
From the plane, how to do?
Let me make a paper-plane
with the telefactor.
Seems very interesting.
So let's begin right away!
Nobita, are you ready?
Yes!
Get going!
It's flying...
So wonderful!
Right, let's go to invite Shizuka to
play with us!
Doraemon
Let me fly to Shizuka's home first!
O.K.
Shizuka
What?
Hello!
It's Nobita!
Shizuka, would you like to play
the game of bailing?
Seems very interesting!
So boring!
Really boring!
Is there anything interesting?
Gian, have a look, someone are
sitting on a paper-plane!
Hey, Gian, come on!
Let's play the game of bailing.
It's Nobita and Shizuka.
Suneo, it seems very interesting!
Let's go to have a look!
They're jumping!
So cool! Please let us join with you!
Then let's play together.
Okay!
Only jumping is a little boring.
Let's have a match!
Who lands on the ground latest will
win! How about the rule?
Good! Seems very interesting.
That's a deal!
I'll try my best.
Let me be your umpire on the ground.
Are you ready?
On your marks!
Go!
So great...
Wow, the houses seem too small!
Just like sitting on a real plane.
It has come to so high!
Much higher!
Let's jump from a very high place,
then I'll win!
I can't! It doesn't matter that I would
lose.
Let's jump here!
I can't stand!
So horrible!
I can't bear with it anymore!
If it keeps rising, I won't stand!
No problem with such a height!
I must win!
He's jumped!
Gian was the last one.
His heavy weight becomes a shortcoming.
Shizuka was the 3rd.
Suneo was the 2nd.
What's happened to Nobita?
Where did he go on earth?
I got fastened onto the balloon!
Anyone come to help me!
Nobita's coming down!
Nobita, you're very awesome!
I've changed my opinion for you.
So cool!
Nothing awesome!
Seasons Can
It's so hot, I'm melting!
It's well enough that there's the
Air conditioning in our house.
But not cool at all.
Why don't you open the Air conditioning?
It doesn't work.
Doesn't work?
All is because we bought the
Air conditioning made by Chanku.
Stop complaining!
Since it becomes very hot today.
Not like in Summer.
If you calm down,
you'll feel cool naturally.
So hot...
Doraemon, you should do something.
Isn't he in? Geez!
Do you have any fans?
What's this?
Seems like a can.
Open it!
So thermal...l was scalded.
What's this? Very thermal...
It hurts...
What problem do you have?
Doraemon, hurry to come up
with some idea! So hot...
I nearly can't stand!
Nothing can be done!
How can you open a Summer Can in Summer
Summer Can
This is called Seasons Can.
This is a combined Cans gift-box.Someone
gave it to me, but I nearly forgot it.
There're Spring, Summer, Fall, Winter.
Once you open a can,
one of the seasons will appear.
And it can last 8 hours.
So open the Spring Can.
It blows the warm wind of Spring.
Feels very comfortable.
Right!
Look, there's a cherry blossom tree
in the neighbor's yard, right?
Yes.
Put the can beside the tree.
Wow, it's blooming.
This one is the Fall.
It blows the wind of Fall.
Feels very cool!
Put it beside the persimmon tree
in the next yard.
It's yielding fruit.
In such a hot day,
we should open the Winter Can.
It's not the true Winter in fact. Only
decorating that atmosphere.
It becomes very cool,
feels very comfortable.
It's very good.
So cold.
So cold, it's too cold.
What do you say, don't make a nonsense!
But it's true.
Are there such cans like that?
Have a look!
Mom, would you like to try?
May I?
Please...
Thank you.
It's a little cold, but I like Winter
most.
Right!
Let's make the whole house to be
in Winter, okay?
Huh...
Who did put the strange stuff here?
It's Doraemon, right?
Is it okay?
Doraemon
Please don't take such things back to
home!
I made the comfortable temperature
specially.
No matter how hot or cold,
you should bear with it.
Anyway I'll give you Summer.
What, you said Summer?
It's good!
Also here!
To make the whole house in Summer!
Geez! We've worked so hard to cool it
down.
I need Winter.
No, Summer is better.
What are you saying, I need Winter.
No, Summer.
I need Winter.
I need Summer.
Must be Winter.
Winter
Summer
I said I need Winter.
Please don't go too far!
How to do?
Because of the strange can which you
threw, my yard got in a mess.
Geez!
Please care about your neighbor
occasionally. You really piss me off!
Sorry.
We're blamed!
The Proud Nobita.
But listen to me!
Unnecessary, although you said so,
it's not the truth.
Not like what you thought, I mean...
it's not like that...
I feel that it's not like this.
I've heard what you said just now.
In my opinion, that affair is...
Nobita, the adults are talking,
you kid, don't disturb!
Have you tidied up your room?
What're you doing?
Stop slacking off, hurry to tidy up
your things.
Things were thrown everywhere.
I don't know how to tidy up!
It's true.
But it's really very difficult to
tidy up the house.
It stands to reason!
Because your things are all piled
in the drawer and bookcase.
At first put the things you don't need
in this box.
Like this.
Put it in the drawer.
This box is very heavy!
Although very easy to say that,
it's really difficult for a kid to
tidy up tings.
Let me do it when I grow up!
What joke are you cutting?
If you do as what you said, this room
will be like a laystall for ever.
Right, I got a good idea!
I know what you got.
You want to find the adult yourself in
the future to give you a hand, right?
Sure it is!
See ya!
Will there be such a good thing?
It hurts.
It hurts...
Look, just as what I said.
How could it be??!
He hits himself! What an unkind guy!
If the former you comes to
ask you to help him to clean,
Will you go?
I'll say to him, 'I'm very busy!' Then
give him a licking and drive him away!
Look, even you said like this.
Of course you would be blamed.
Right...
Let me change the current myself to
be an adult with the Time Cloth.
Change to be an adult!
This is nothing at all.
Even much higher place,
I can't put things on it.
Doraemon, don't stand by only.
Hurry to do me a favor.
Okay.
After tidying it up, you need wipe it
with the rag.
Geez, you become very cocky
after you change to be an adult.
Have a look...
If you do, it'll be done.
It's become very clean.
That's too great!
Actually you ordered me to do all
the things.
I'm really very clever!
Let me keep myself like this!
What, like this?
It doesn't matter, I got a good idea.
Pop's clothes are very suitable for you.
Although it's true,
listen to me!
I've tidied up the room on 2nd floor.
Thank you.
Good work!
So I'm out to play, see you!
What's that person just now?
Who do you say he is, it couldn't be
that you...
Because he seemed to be very familiar
with us. I thought you knew him.
I thought he's one of your relative.
My neighbor uncle!
I'm taller than you!
I don't know you! None of your business.
Really good!
Feels that the world becomes very
spacious.
Hey, Gian!
So weird!
Who's this uncle?
I don't know!
You always said cocky that you're
very strong.
If you have a sumo match with me,
will you win?
Impossible!
Don't say that so early!
Let's have a match.
Stop...
I won Gian!
It stands to reason!
Are you going to play baseball?
Let me join in you, okay?
What?
Fair hit!
Here!
Fair hit, the stickman was out!
Being an adult,
I still played very poor.
It's so hard to get such a good chance.
You're an adult, but you're really
useless.
Shut up, stop making the rubbish!
Don't be like this! It's too shameful
for an adult.
Weird, I'm just here! Why are you here?
Never mind, hurry to go back...
An adult riding the high horse here
went really too far!
Awesome! Nobita is teaching that man
a lesson.
None of your business, hurry to go back...
Hurry to go back.
Nobita, you're so cool!
You drove him away finally.
We're feeling bored since being
entwined by that weird guy.
Okay, hurry to recover normal.
Next let me go by the Time Machine to
see what happened 15 minutes ago.
Okay!
Fair hit!
I'm hitting...
Fair hit! The stickman was out!
Sure enough it's still the Strikeout.
It's so hard to get such a good chance.
You're an adult, but you're really
useless.
Shut up, stop making the rubbish!
An adult came to play with kids,
but so self-righteous!
That's too shameful!
Don't be like this! It's too shameful
for an adult.
Weird, I'm just here! Why are you here?
Never mind, hurry to go back...
An adult riding the high horse here
went really too far!
Hurry to go back.
No matter how many times I play,
I can't play well yet!
Collecting Bottle Cover
I showed this to you, you should
appreciate me very much.
I've worked so hard in order to get
this.
Yikuni
It's just that famous stamp...
worthy of 18000 Yen...
which all the collectors want to get.
If it's the collection of tags, I'll be
more confident than the others.
My collection of money is also not bad.
So it is.
I remembered something to do
suddenly, so I'm going home!
Money, what's it for?
To buy the stamp?
Didn't you give up to collect
the stamps?
Mom said 'In either case you'll say
not to want to collect anymore'.
Don't do anything needless'
I feel that it stands to reason!
But how shameful! I have no
any collection to be proud!
Right!
Don't you have some outstanding
collection?
Are you pointing me?
Yes!
When and what have I collected?
Well!
What, it's a bottle cover!
Idiot, you're laughing at me
with such thing?
Not at all!
How do you decide the value of
something?
In the end it's decided by
that people want it or not!
At the beginning if people didn't
want the stamps and jewels,
they would be some ordinary paper and
stones.
And...So...what do you want to say?
I want to monkey tricks!
The epidemical virus.
What? Didn't we use it before?
Yes!
What's it for?
This virus can be born only in 1 minute.
During this time, you need to say
what you hope to be popular.
Collecting Bottle Cover
So it is!
Then spreading it by wind.
It'll act well at once!
I'm going out to take a view.
Look. . . I've collected 3.
I've collected 5.
But I've collected one dozen.
One dozen!
Have a look, what I collected.
The printing is skew.
Such things will be very valuable.
You're so awesome that you could
collect such thing.
Really foolish!
Everyone doesn't know that they've
caught the epidemical virus.
What do you collect these things for?
Don't touch them!
You should use the clamp.
In case that the bottle covers would
get rusty.
This guy can't yet catch up
with the fashion.
It's very popular for now to collect
this.
It has been outdated to collect
the stamps or coins.
Look at the beautiful form and
the interesting pattern!
You won't get boring, even
watching it for one whole day.
To collect the bottle covers will create
the worldwide fashion right away.
Never thought it would be so serious.
The effective is really awesome.
Nobita, what did you say?
Nothing!
Right, everyone, come to my home!
All of these are Nobita's collection?
When did you collect them?
Nothing splendid!
Just I've noticed something different
from yours.
Because Nobita's thought is very
advanced!
I give up!
All right!
Hurry to collect!
Really interesting!
I'm in a very good mood! Doraemon
Mom, I'll beg you only this time in my
life!
From today on let's replace all the
snacks and meals with Coca-cola!
Finally I've collected more than
10 bottle covers.
But I nearly spited out Coca-cola
when I was hiccupping.
Next I'm going to collect the bottle
covers of the carbonated drinks.
Please drink to the top of your bend!
You opened so many bottles,
how can I drink up?
I got 26!
I got 50!
No...you don't know the method
for collecting at all.
It has no any significance to only
collect many.
Yes!
In despite of the stamps or anything
else, a little will be money's worth.
Is that so?
For example, among Nobita's collection,
the bottle cover of Coca-cola which he
bought at Sankowu on 12th August...
is the only one in the world
among those...
were sold at Sankowu at that day.
1 million Yen, no, even you pay
10 million, you won't buy it.
Really interesting!
Everyone started to collect the bottle
covers.
Yes!
Nobita, a gift for you!
This is a bottle cover of some sport
drink. It values 2 thousand Yen!
What?
The virus seems spreading very seriously
Even Papa has caught it.
How long will the effective last?
It's almost time to finish it.
Nobita is in for sure!
I'm collecting the Bottle Covers
specially.
Just because of the rumor I came to
visit you.
It's heard that you got
a splendid bottle cover.
For the bottle cover of the Coca-cola
you bought at Sankowu on 12th August
I'll pay 2 million Yen to you.
What, 2 million?
I can't sell it to you.
You dislike the price?
Then 3 million!
How can it be?!
You won't?
So 5 million!
Then 7 million?
8 million!
How about a check of 10 million?
Is it enough? Yep!
Thank you, I bought it finally!
Was it good to sell that 10 million Yen?
Why did I pay 10 million Yen for
such a thing?
Really something wrong with me!
The effective of the virus has
finished up.
Feels very regrettable!
But also feels relaxed.
This result is really too good.
Sure it is!